For the “printmenu” define function, it prints out the choices of the bank menu including the “===“ to separate the menu from previous data. For the main function, it starts off with initial balance of the user, which is 1000, and set the user choice to 0. When the user enter any choices that is not equal to 4, then the program will start run through the choices. The first try block runs the user’s input, then the except block will allow the program to continue even if the user does not enter an option. The except block will print a statement showing the that option that the user enter is not valid, and tells the user to re-enter a new option. In the if and else function, set the invalid variable to true in order to operate the try-except statement. The first if function runs when user enters the option 1, which is to withdraw from the bank. If the user enter a value that is not an integer, the program won’t crash because of the except block. The second try-except statement in the second else if function works the same way as the first if function, but the second if function runs when user enters option 2, which is for user to make deposit. For the third if function, it allows user to print their balance. Once the user enters option 4, the program closes. If user enters any option that is not between 1 and 4, then the program prints that it is not a valid option, and ask the user to re-enter a valid option. 